Guide to the Polly Shackleton papers, 1894-1997 MS2031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject, chronological and correspondence files, 1970-1987; Series 10
  - Files H-M, 1970-1987; Series 10 Subseries 4
    - Legislation No - Fault Amendments, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Legislation No - Fault Implementation, 1982-1983; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Legislation No - Fault Implementation, 1983; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Legislation No - Fault Ins., 1983; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Legislation No - Fault Ins., 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Legislation No - Fault Ins., 1983; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Legislation No - Fault Ins. Letters from Polly Shackleton, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Legislation No - Fault Insurance, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Legislation No - Fault Letters Against, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Legislation No - Fault Letters Against, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Legislation No - Fault Letters Against, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Legislation No - Fault Letters For, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Legislation No - Fault Letters For, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Legislation No Fault Ins., 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Legislation No Fault Ins., 1982-1983; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Legislation No Fault Insurance, 1989; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Legislation No Fault Insurance, 1982-1983; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Legislation No Fault Insurance, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Legislation No Fault Insurance, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Legislation No Fault Insurance, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Legislation No Fault Insurance, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Lobby - ERA, 1976; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Lobby - Lie Detector Bill, 1978; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Lobby Abortions, 1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Lobby Abortions, 1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Lobby Abortions, 1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Lobby Adoptees Record Act Inspection of 2 - 238, 1978; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Lobby Arts and Culture Subcommittee, 1978; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Lobby Bill 2 - 101, 1977-1978; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Lobby Bill 2 - 188, 1976-1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Lobby Clean Air Indoor Act, 1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Lobby Condominium Conversion, 1979-1980; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Lobby Demolition Approval Procedure, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Lobby Early Retirement, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Lobby Estate Tax, 1979-1981; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Lobby Estate Tax, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Lobby Families with Childrean Equal Rights act of '80, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Lobby Gas Tax, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Lobby General, 1975-1978; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Lobby General, 1978-1979; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Lobby General, 1979; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Lobby Gross Reciepts Tax, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Lobby Gross Reciepts Tax, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Lobby Gross Reciepts Tax, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Lobby Gun Control, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Lobby Gun Control, 1976; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Lobby Gun Control, 1979-1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Lobby Historic Mostor Vehicle Act, 1976-1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Lobby Historical Land Marks, 1978; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Lobby L Bus Line, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Lobby L Bus Line, 1982-1983; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Lobby Legalized Gambling, 1975-1979; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Lobby Metrobus Changes, 1981-1983; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Lobby Metrobus Changes, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Lobby Metrobus Changes, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Lobby Minority Contractors Bill of 1976 (1 - 123), Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Lobby Motor Vehicle Insurance, 1979-1980; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Lobby Motor Vehicle Insurance, 1980-1981; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Lobby Pension Funds - Teachers, 1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Lobby Personnel Bill, 1978; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Lobby Probate, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Lobby Real Property Tax Exemption Act of 1980, Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Lobby Rent Control, 1972-1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Lobby Rent Control, 1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Lobby Retirement Funds (HR 2465), 1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Lobby Sales Tax Act (3 - 149), 1979; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Lobby Teachers Lobby Bill #2 - 187, 1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Lobby Teachers Retirement, 1975-1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Lobby University of DC, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Lobby Usury Rate, 1979; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Lobby Voter Registration, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Lobby Workmans Compensation, 1979-1980; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Massage Parlors, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Massage Parlors, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Massage Parlors, 1976-1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - MP - Misc., 1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - MP - Misc., 1976; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - MP - Misc., 1977-1978; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - MP - Misc., 1979; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - MP - Misc., 1980; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - MP - Misc., 1983-1984; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - MP Parking, 1976; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - MP Parking, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - MP Parking, 1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - MP Parking, 1978; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - MP Parking, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - MP Traffic, 1975-1977; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - MP/Public Relations, 1975-1983; Series 10 Subseries 4 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Files N-Z, numerical, 1970-1987; Series 10 Subseries 5
    - New Release April - June, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - News Relase May - June, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - News Release, 1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - News Release, 1984; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - News Release August - December, 1979; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - News Release February - May, 1979; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - News Release January - February, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - News Release January - March, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - News Release January - March, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - News Release July - August, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - News Release July - September, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - News Release June - July, 1979; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - News Release March - April, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - News Release November - December, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - News Release November - December, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - News Release October - December, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - OCF Amendments, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Office Log, 1976; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - PS/CA Hearing, Vendors Registration Amendment, Bill 4 - 480, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - PS/CA Mark - up Bill 4 - 35, "Cable TV Communication Act", 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - PS/CA Mark - up Bill 4 - 35, "Cable TV Communication Act", 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - PS/CA Meeting - Funeral Prices, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - PS/CA Meeting Withdrawn from agenda; make - up of Nurse Practice Act, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - PS/CA Oversight Hearing Insurance, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - PS/CA Roundtable Bill 4 - 272 Liquor License Limitation, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - PS/CA Roundtable D.C. Midwifery Practice, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Questionaires 1982 Election, Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Re - Election, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - REC, 1984-1985; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - REC, 1978-1984; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - REC, 1975-1977; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - REC, 1977-1978; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Redistricting and Utilities, 1982-1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Public Hearing Bill 4 - 181 Committee of the Whole, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Public Roundtable Committee of the Whole, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Public Roundtable Testimony, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Redistricting, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Redistricting, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Redistricting ANCS, 1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Redistricting ANCS, 1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Redistricting ANCS, 1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Utilities, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Utilities, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Utilities II, 1981-1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Utilities II, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Utilities III, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Utilities III, 1981-1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Redistricting and Utilities Water and Sewer Service Repairs, 1976-1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Redistricting and Utlities Committee of the Whole, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Redistricting and Utlities Legislation, Amendments, Alternatives, Proposals, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Redistricting and Utlities Legislation, Amendments, Alternatives, Proposals, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Redistricting Utilities Redistricting (ANCs), 1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Redistricting Utilities Redistricting (ANCs), 1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Redistricting Utilities Redistricting (ANCs), 1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Redistricting Utilities Redistricting Background Info, News, Articles, 1981-1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Redistricting Utilities Redistricting Lobby/Correspodence, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Rent Control, 1985; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Rhodes Tavern Letters, 1983-1984; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Special Subject ANC 3E, 1979; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Subject Files: CS/Budget, 1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Subject Files: ECD/ABC Board, 1975-1979; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files: ECD/Licenses & Permits, 1975-1976; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Subject Files: ES/Alley Cleaning, 1979; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Subject Files: ES/Catch Basins (Sewer), 1975-1978; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Subject Files: ES/Environmental Health Administration, 1979-1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Subject Files: ES/Health and Sanitation Inspection, 1971-1979; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Subject Files: ES/Leaf Removal, 1974-1978; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Subject Files: ES/Snow Removal, 1978-1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Subject Files: ES/Trash, 1976-1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Subject FilesPS/CA Item Prices, 1981-1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - T/EA Cable TV Hearing, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - T/EA General 1, 1981-1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - T/EA General 2, 1982-1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - T/EA Hearing Air Quality, 1982-1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - T/EA Hearing Air Quality 2, 1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - T/EA Hearing Air Quality 3, 1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - T/EA Hearing Reorganization Surveyor's Office, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - T/EA Meeting Alley Closings, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - T/EA Meeting RPP, Whitehaven Park, Surveyor, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - T/EA Meeting Staggered Register Street/Alley Closing Procedures etc, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Thank you letters, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Thank you letters, 1976; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Thank you letters, 1977; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Thank you letters, 1979; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Thank you letters, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Thank you letters, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Thank you letters, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Trees and Landscaping, 1978; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Trees and Landscaping, 1977-1978; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Unemployment Compensation Act, 1971-1978; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Zoning - Alley Closing 1, 1980-1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Zoning - Alley Closing 2, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Zoning - Commission, 1978-1979; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Zoning - Commission Cases, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Zoning - Commission Cases, 1983; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Zoning - Commission Cases, 1984; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Zoning - Commission Cases, 1985; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Zoning - Conversations, 1980-1981; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Zoning - Hearing Notices, 1978-1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Zoning - Planning, 1976-1978; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Zoning - Planning 1, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Zoning - Planning 2, 1975-1978; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Zoning - Planning and Development Ward 3, Undated; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Zoning - Plannnig Ward 3, 1976; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Zoning - Redevelopment land agency, 1981-1982; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Zoning - Rhodes Tavern 1, 1978-1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Zoning - Rhodes Tavern 2, 1978-1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Zoning - Rhodes Tavern 3, 1982-1985; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Zoning - Tax Assessment, 1976-1978; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Zoning Cases - California Joe's, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Zoning Hearing Notices, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Zoning Hearing Notices, 1981-1984; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Zoning Land Use Planning, 1976-1978; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Zoning News Release, 1976; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Zoning Variance, 1981-1984; Series 10 Subseries 5 (Box 139, Folder 5)